The Gilbert and Lila Silverman Fluxus Collection Archives
The Museum of Modern Art, Publisher
- Series I: Artists, Personalities, and Groups, 1952-2012
  - Hans Hartmann, 1965, 1987, undated; Ephemera and pamphlets acquired from estate of Hans Hartmann. (Box 36, Folder I.478)
  - Hans Hartmann, 1962-1964; News clippings acquired from estate of Hans Hartmann. (Box 36, Folder I.479)
  - Hans Hartmann, 1992-1995; News clippings and ephemera acquired from estate of Hans Hartmann. (Box 36, Folder I.480)
  - Hans Hartmann, 1991-1999; News clippings and ephemera acquired from estate of Hans Hartmann. (Box 36, Folder I.481)
  - Lee Hefflin, 1967; Correspondence and works sent to Ken Friedman. (Box 36, Folder I.482)
  - Bici Forbes Hendricks, 1966, 1971, 1989; Includes "Statement of Aims and Purposes of the Black Thumb Press" (1966); polaroid snapshots of Bici Forbes Hendricks taken by Hendricks (1989); photocopy and copy negative of portrait.; Note: Bici Forbes Hendricks is also known as Nye Ffarrabas. (Box 36, Folder I.483)
  - Geoffrey Hendricks, 1966-1993, 2008-2009; Includes collaborations with Nye Ffarrabas [Bici Forbes Hendricks]. Includes material regarding "The Friday Book of White Noise;" photos; correspondence (original and photocopy); ephemera; exhibition announcements. (Box 36, Folder I.484)
  - Geoffrey Hendricks, undated; Photocopies, copy photographs, and transparencies of works, produced by the collection for publication use, with collection notes. (Box 36, Folder I.485)
  - Henri Gallery, 1967, undated; Correspondence from Richard C. (Box 36, Folder I.486)
  - Henri Gallery, 1967-1973, 1981, undated; Correspondence and ephemera. Includes letter to Silverman from Henri (Henrietta Ehrsam) about Henri Gallery materials (8/17/1981). (Box 36, Folder I.487)
  - Henri Gallery, 1972; L.A. artists' publication(October 1972). (Box 36, Folder I.488)
  - Hi Red Center, [1966]; "Record of Features and Feats," includes worksheets from Flux Clinic event and photocopies of worksheets for On Kawara and "Hiraoka." Accession #s:[00.14] (Box 36, Folder I.489)
  - Hi Red Center, undated; Velox of Genpei Akasegawa's face for Bundle of Events; negatives for Hotel Event at Waldorf Astoria poster; with notes from Hendricks. (Box 36, Folder I.490)
  - Hi Red Center, 1982, 1965; Hendricks notes and other material from meeting with Jiro Takamatsu and Genpei Akasegawa, 1982. Includes poster by Maciunas and Shigeko Kubota for Bundle of Events(1965). (Box 36, Folder I.491)
  - Hi Red Center, undated; Photocopies, copy photographs, and transparencies of works, produced by the collection for publication use, with collection notes. (Box 36, Folder I.492)
  - Dick Higgins, 1962-1966; Photocopies and typed transcriptions of Maciunas correspondence to Dick Higgins. (Box 36, Folder I.493)
  - Dick Higgins, 1962-1978; Photocopies of correspondence to Maciunas; 1 ALS regarding "Penny Piece" (6/19/1971). (Box 37, Folder I.494)
  - Dick Higgins, 1963-1982, 2009; Correspondence, includes to Philip Corner (photocopy); Albert Fine; Allan Kaprow; Arthur Køpcke; Knud Pedersen; Florence Tarlow; Ben Vautier; Robert Watts (with reply); also ALS Hermann Braun - Hendricks (photocopy, 1/3/2009). Accession #s: 90.14 (Box 37, Folder I.495)
  - Dick Higgins, 1966-1980; Correspondence with Ken Friedman. Includes "Thirteen Serious Considerations" (1978). (Box 37, Folder I.496)
  - Dick Higgins, 1959; Two papers on William Carlos Williams. (Box 37, Folder I.497)
  - Dick Higgins, 1960-1982; Includes concert programs; exhibition announcements; photocopies of writings. (Box 37, Folder I.498)
  - Dick Higgins, 1979, 1995; "Bio/Bibliography." (Box 37, Folder I.499)
  - Dick Higgins, 1965; "A Book About Love & War & Death" (1965). Includes Great Bear Pamphlet; two copies of typescript draft. (Box 37, Folder I.500)
  - Dick Higgins, 1988; Insurance papers for "Requiem for Wagner" (1962) sent from Dick Higgins to Hendricks. (Box 37, Folder I.501)
  - Dick Higgins, 1982; "A Fluxessay for a Few of my Fluxfriends," typescript. (Box 37, Folder I.502)
  - Dick Higgins, 1966-1971; Something Else Press newsletters. Includes annotated typescripts for "Intermedia" (February 1966) and "Structural Researches" (April 1968). (Box 37, Folder I.503)
  - Dick Higgins, after 1973; Something Else Press history, 1963-1973, annotated typescript. (Box 37, Folder I.504)
  - Dick Higgins, 1964; "Postface," annotated typescript sent to Wolf Vostell by Dick Higgins. (Box 37, Folder I.505)
  - Dick Higgins, 1961; "A New Novel about Syphaloon Endestuary," annotated typescript. (Box 37, Folder I.506)
  - Dick Higgins, undated; Unidentified notes. (Box 37, Folder I.507)
  - Dick Higgins, 1963; "The Tart or Miss America," flyer and typescript instructions. (Box 37, Folder I.508)
  - Dick Higgins, 1962; "Broadway Opera," concert program and photocopy of score. (Box 37, Folder I.509)
  - Dick Higgins, 1961-1982, 1991-1994; Includes photograph of Higgins's Christopher Street apartment; photocopy of "Three Dramas for George" ([1961?]/1991); mailings; ephemera. (Box 37, Folder I.510)
  - Dick Higgins, after 1979; "Around the World in a Minesweeper, or A Few Observations on Fluxus," typescript. (Box 38, Folder I.511)
  - Dick Higgins, 1982; "Fluxus: Theory and Reception," typescript. (Box 38, Folder I.512)
  - Dick Higgins, 1966; "The Fabulous World of Typhoon-Willie"/"Die Fabelhafte Getraeume von Taifun-Willi," annotated typescript for a "radio Happening," with letter to Ken Friedman. (Box 38, Folder I.513)
  - Dick Higgins, 1967; East Village Other, Vol. 2 No. 28, with article by Dick Higgins, "Can Art Be Far Behind?" (Box 38, Folder I.514)
  - Dick Higgins, 1967; "Some Graphis Mirrors," 2 copies. (Box 38, Folder I.515)
  - Dick Higgins, 1982-1983; Piano Sonata #2 (Graphic #192) (1982); Song for an voice(s) and instruments(s) (Graphic 192b) (1983). Printed scores. (Box 38, Folder I.516)
  - Dick Higgins, 1960; Cabarets, Contributions, Einschlusz. Event program/score and performance photograph. (Box 38, Folder I.517)
  - Dick Higgins, 1959-1966; News clippings regarding performances; program for Something Else concert (1965); "Proposed Program for a Fluxfest in Prague, 1966," Fluxus mailing. (Box 38, Folder I.518)
  - Dick Higgins, undated; Photocopies, copy photographs, and transparencies of works, produced by the collection for publication use, with collection notes. (Box 38, Folder I.519)
  - Dick Higgins, 1963, 1986, undated; Includes prospectus for "Graphis 82 kit" (1986); text for Graphis 118; ccontact sheets of photographs of unidentified Fluxus performance; notes by Dick Higgins from letter to John Hunov (1963). Accession #s: 00.01, 00.20, 93.08 (Box 38, Folder I.520)
  - Dick Higgins, 1961; Typescript for 100 Plays, 102 pages. Accession #s: 00.01 (Box 38, Folder I.521)
  - Dick Higgins, undated; 1 of 2 containing annotated typescript for Postface, pages 1-40. Accession #s: 94.10 (Box 38, Folder I.522)
  - Dick Higgins, undated; 2 of 2 containing annotated typescript for Postface, pages 41-83. Accession #s: 94.10 (Box 38, Folder I.523)
  - Dick Higgins, 1960-1968, undated; Texts and mailings once belonging to Arthur Køpcke. Accession #s: 96.18 (Box 38, Folder I.524)
  - Dick Higgins, 1965-1968; Ephemera and pamphlets of the Something Else Press acquired from estate of Hans Hartmann. (Box 38, Folder I.525)
  - Dick Higgins, 1966-1972; The Something Else Newsletter, vol. 1, nos. 1 and 5-11; vol. 2, nos. 1-5. Acquired from estate of Hans Hartmann. (Box 38, Folder I.526)
  - Dick Higgins, 1965-1972; Ephemera, including for the Something Else Gallery, acquired from estate of Hans Hartmann. (Box 38, Folder I.527)
  - Dick Higgins, 1960, 1964-1965; Ephemera, including order form for Jefferson's Birthday/Postface; "Zeichen-Spiele," German translation of "Design Plays" (1960). (Box 38, Folder I.528)
  - Dick Higgins, undated; "An Anomymous Novel About the Snow," 10 pages. (Box 38, Folder I.529)
  - Dick Higgins, 1969; "assignments" ("old version"). (Box 38, Folder I.530)
  - Dick Higgins, 1979; "as: another seven," 1 page. (Box 38, Folder I.531)
  - Dick Higgins, undated; "Musarum Liber XXV Urania," book. (Box 38, Folder I.532)
  - Dick Higgins, 1969; "Blank Images and Otherwise," 11 pages. (Box 38, Folder I.533)
  - Dick Higgins, 1968; "Blank Images," 2 copies. (Box 38, Folder I.534)
  - Dick Higgins, 1981; "A Book," 5 pages. (Box 38, Folder I.535)
  - Dick Higgins, undated; "Book bells, slowly moving," 23 pages. (Box 38, Folder I.536)
  - Dick Higgins, 1971; "City with all the angles: a radio play," 48 pages. (Box 39, Folder I.537)
  - Dick Higgins, 1966; "Colloquial and sentimental edifices," 10 page text (1960) and printed article in underground(November 1966). (Box 39, Folder I.538)
  - Dick Higgins, 1981-1982, undated; "Danger Musics," folder of collages and correspondence. (Box 39, Folder I.539)
  - Dick Higgins, 1981; "A Fluxessay for a Few of my Fluxfriends," photocopy, 8 pages. (Box 39, Folder I.540)
  - Dick Higgins, 1976-1978; gilles, text about performance, contact sheets, and filmstrips from performance at the Whitney Museum. (Box 39, Folder I.541)
  - Dick Higgins, 1985; "Glue Mama's Best Munchies," score enclosed with letter to Linda Weintraub (11/5/1985). (Box 39, Folder I.542)
  - Dick Higgins, undated; Typescript, 29 pages, described by Hendricks as "German text translated by Eckart Rahn on Happenings and Fluxus." (Box 39, Folder I.543)
  - Dick Higgins, 1971; "mice all over the place," 9 pages. (Box 39, Folder I.544)
  - Dick Higgins, undated; "The Noun 'Happening'" ("school version"), 20 pages. (Box 39, Folder I.545)
  - Dick Higgins, 1967; "Le Petit Cirque au fin du Monde," photocopy, 21 pages. (Box 39, Folder I.546)
  - Dick Higgins, 1976; "The Post-Cognitive Era: Looking for the Sense in it All," 9 pages. (Box 39, Folder I.547)
  - Dick Higgins, 1978; "Postmodern Performance: Some Criteria and Common Points," 15 pages. (Box 39, Folder I.548)
  - Dick Higgins, 1977; ICA Magazine no. 6 (1977), with contributions from Dick Higgins and Robert Filliou. (Box 39, Folder I.549)
  - Dick Higgins, 1968-1981; Magazines with articles by Dick Higgins. (Box 39, Folder I.550)
  - Dick Higgins, 1982-1985; Magazines with articles by Dick Higgins. (Box 39, Folder I.551)
  - Dick Higgins, 1977; "six trivial reflections," photcopy, 4 pages. (Box 39, Folder I.552)
  - Dick Higgins, undated; Printer's proof of "Spring Game," 17 pages. (Box 39, Folder I.553)
  - Dick Higgins, undated; "The Strategy of Visual Poetry: Three Aspects," 19 pages. (Box 39, Folder I.554)
  - Dick Higgins, 1977; "Towards an Allusive Deferential," 9 pages. (Box 39, Folder I.555)
  - Dick Higgins, 1978; "Thirteen Serious Considerations," 17 cards in envelope. (Box 39, Folder I.556)
  - Dick Higgins, undated; "Twenty Seven Episodes for the Aquarian Theater." (Box 39, Folder I.557)
  - Dick Higgins, 1976; "Two Essays Written on May 16, 1976," photocopy. (Box 39, Folder I.558)
  - Dick Higgins, 1969; "Death and the Nickle Cigar: a lickety split mystery," bound typescript, 154 pages. (Box 40, Folder I.559)
  - Dick Higgins, 1969-1986, undated; Includes ephemera, texts, articles, and notes. (Box 40, Folder I.560)
  - Dick Higgins, 1966; Copy of letter exchange between Dick Higgins, Maciunas, and Jeff Berner Inventory #s: 01318 (Box 40, Folder I.561)
  - Dick Higgins, 1966-1978; Essays by Dick Higgins; "An Analytical Checklist of Books from Something Else Press" in Small Press Review by Hugh Fox (1974); Something Else Press newsletters. (Box 40, Folder I.562)
  - Dick Higgins, 1963-1978; Ephemera, essays, and texts, including set of yellow text postcards mailed to Knud Pedersen (1978); "Computers for the Arts" (1970); "Some Graphis Mirrors" (1967); "iron-on" labels published by Vice-Versand (1969). Inventory #s: 02563 (Box 40, Folder I.563)
  - Dick Higgins, undated; "Employment Questionnaire." (Box 40, Folder I.564)
  - Dick Higgins, 1962-1964; "The Tart, or Miss America," includes photocopies of photographs, tickets, correspondence to Dick Higgins, news clippings, and typescript. (Box 40, Folder I.565)
  - Dick Higgins, 1962-1965; "The Tart, or Miss America," "a scherzo or maybe a sermon of some kind," text, contact sheets by Peter Moore, and news clipings. (Box 40, Folder I.566)
  - Dick Higgins, [1965]; "The Tart, or Miss America," ephemera. (Box 40, Folder I.567)
  - Dick Higgins, 1960, undated; "Stacked Deck," text for opera by Dick Higgins and Richard Maxfield and news clippings. (Box 40, Folder I.568)
  - Dick Higgins, 1960; Dick Higgins's Bachelor of Science degree, conferred by Columbia University. (Box 40, Folder I.569)
  - Davi Det Hompson, 1972, 1993-1996; Correspondence with Hendricks, plus enclosed cards and works, including "There's Music in My Soles" (1972). (Box 41, Folder I.570)
  - Davi Det Hompson, 1976-1977, 1982-1983; Books by Hompson, acquired from J.N. Herlin. Also includes TLS Davi Det Hompson - Ken Friedman (7/28/1982). (Box 41, Folder I.571)
  - Davi Det Hompson, 1966; Cover of Fold Out, 8 copies ("David Thompson/Fluxus"). (Box 41, Folder I.572)
  - Armin Hundertmark, 1970-1986; Correspondence to Ken Friedman, mostly regarding works for publication by Edition Hundertmark. Includes advertisements and catalogues for editions for sale, including by Joseph Beuys, Milan Knžk, Gerhard Rhm, Hermann Nitsch, Ben Vautier, Tomas Schmit, Eric Anderson. (Box 41, Folder I.573)
  - Armin Hundertmark, 1969-1976; Correspondence to Arthur Køpcke, including on poscards, collage, and Edition Hundertmark stationery. In German. Inventory #s: 06044.1-13 (Box 41, Folder I.574)
  - John Hunov, 1961-1967, undated; Includes festival and exhibition news clippings (originally from Galerie Køpcke?) acquired from John Hunov; letter to Køpcke (undated). Accession #s: 00.20 (Box 41, Folder I.575)
  - Alice Hutchins, 1967-1968, 1986-1989; Includes photographs by Peter Moore of works by Alice Hutchins, sent by Alice Hutchins to Hendricks; correspondence to Hendricks, Ken Friedman, Alison Knowles, Maciunas (photocopy). Accession #s: 89.03 (Box 41, Folder I.576)
  - Dorothy Iannone, 1970; Ephemera mailed to Arthur Køpcke (11/25/1970). (Box 41, Folder I.577)
  - Toshi Ichiyanagi, 1960-1963; Photocopies of scores. (Box 41, Folder I.578)
  - Toshi Ichiyanagi, 1961-1963; Photocopy and transcript of ALS Maciunas - Toshi Ichiyanagi (12/8/1961); photocopy of Maciunas notes on Toshi Ichiyanagi. (Box 41, Folder I.579)
  - Tatu Izumi, 1963; Mailing to Galerie Parnass, including photographs for model of Naiqua Gallery. (Box 41, Folder I.580)
  - Terry Jennings, 1960-1963; Photocopies of scores. (Box 41, Folder I.581)
  - Ray Johnson, 1963-ca. 1965; Correspondence, including to Philip Krumm (photocopy); with Albert Fine to George Brecht. Accession #s: 90.14 (Box 41, Folder I.582)
  - Ray Johnson, 1966-1971; Correspondence to Ken Friedman; ephemera. (Box 41, Folder I.583)
  - Joe Jones, 1970-1980, 1994; Includes correspondence to and from; material regarding Fluxorchestra; interview with Michael Oren (3/18/1978); news clippings; exhibition ephemera. (Box 41, Folder I.584)
  - Joe Jones, ca. 1963; Looseleaf binder with notes, sketches, plans, descriptions of works, news clippings. Inventory #s: 05995-0600, 02387 (Box 42, Folder I.585)
  - Joe Jones, undated; Polaroids of Fluxorchestra instruments taken by Hendricks at the Jean Brown Archive; photocopies, copy photographs, and transparencies of works and portraits, mostly produced by the collection for publication use, with collection notes. (Box 42, Folder I.586)
  - Joe Jones, 1964-1965; News clippings. Accession #s: 04.08 (Box 42, Folder I.587)
  - Clemens Kalischer, 1977, 1987, undated; Contact sheets of Fluxus events, including of events at New Marlborough (1977); correspondence with Hendricks concerning purchase of photographs (1987). (Box 42, Folder I.588)
  - Allan Kaprow, 1962, undated; Photocopy of Maciunas notes on Allan Kaprow (12/16/1962); copy negative and photocopy of portrait. (Box 42, Folder I.589)
  - Allan Kaprow, 1966; Some Recent Happenings(1966). Includes annotated typescript; Great Bear Pamphlet; correspondence with Emmett Williams. (Box 42, Folder I.590)
  - Gyula Keszthelyi, 1972-1974, undated; Correspondence with Ken Friedman, including photographs, works, and translations of Ken Friedman's Events into Hungarian (5/10/1974). (Box 42, Folder I.591)
  - Per Kirkeby, 1968-1973, 1985; Correspondence to Ken Friedman, Arthur Køpcke, Maciunas (photocopy); Polaroid photograph of the artist by Hendricks (1985). (Box 42, Folder I.592)
  - Per Kirkeby, 1993, 2000; Regarding Per Kirkeby works for sale; article on Per Kirkeby in Scanorama, in-flight magazine of Scandinavian Airlines (September, 2000). (Box 42, Folder I.593)
  - Per Kirkeby, undated; Photocopies, copy photographs, and transparencies of works, produced by the collection for publication use, with collection notes. (Box 42, Folder I.594)
  - Per Kirkeby, 1984-1986, 1994-1998, undated; News clippings and ephemera acquired from estate of Hans Hartmann. (Box 42, Folder I.595)
  - Yves Klein, 1963-1964; Ephemera. (Box 42, Folder I.596)
  - Milan Knžk, 1962-1963, undated; 1 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Moveable objects, environments, environments on the street (called then short carting exhibitions)," text in Czech and photographs. Inventory #s:[01939.1-23]; Note: for the originals of these 101 files, see the Department of Prints and Illustrated Books. (Box 42, Folder I.597)
  - Milan Knžk, 1963, undated; 2 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Sance," text in Czech and English and photographs. Inventory #s:[01940.1-12] (Box 42, Folder I.598)
  - Milan Knžk, 1963, undated; 3 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Body and a sculpture," text in Czech and English and photographs. Inventory #s:[01941.1-5] (Box 42, Folder I.599)
  - Milan Knžk, 1963, undated; 4 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Environment in a back-yard," text in Czech and English and photographs. Inventory #s:[01942.1-8] (Box 42, Folder I.600)
  - Milan Knžk, 1964, undated; 5 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "1st manifestation of AA [Aktual Art]", text in Czech and English and photographs. Inventory #s:[01943.1-21] (Box 42, Folder I.601)
  - Milan Knžk, 1963-1964, undated; 6 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "iv Obrazy," text in Czech. (Box 42, Folder I.602)
  - Milan Knžk, 1964, undated; 7 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Demonstration for oneself," text in English. (Box 42, Folder I.603)
  - Milan Knžk, 1964, undated; 8 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Demonstation of oneself," text in English and photographs. Inventory #s:[01944.1-11] (Box 42, Folder I.604)
  - Milan Knžk, 1964, undated; 9 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "The artificial staging og [sic] natural phenomena," text in English. (Box 42, Folder I.605)
  - Milan Knžk, 1964, undated; 10 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "People inside a picture," text in English. (Box 42, Folder I.606)
  - Milan Knžk, 1964, undated; 11 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "The Aktual Walk, Demonstration for All Aense," text in English and photographs. Inventory #s:[01945.1-40] (Box 42, Folder I.607)
  - Milan Knžk, 1964, undated; 12 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Ritus/Passive part of the demonstration," text English. (Box 43, Folder I.608)
  - Milan Knžk, 1964, undated; 13 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Exhibition of articles which I have not created," text in Czech and English and photographs. Inventory #s:[01946.1-18] (Box 43, Folder I.609)
  - Milan Knžk, 1965, undated; 14 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Letters to the public," text in English. (Box 43, Folder I.610)
  - Milan Knžk, 1965, undated; 15 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "I scattered on a Prague street a great amount of papers," text in English. (Box 43, Folder I.611)
  - Milan Knžk, 1965, undated; 16 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Demonstration for J. Mach," text in English and photographs. Inventory #s:[01947.1-41] (Box 43, Folder I.612)
  - Milan Knžk, 1965, undated; 17 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "How to Make Clothing Aktual," text in English. (Box 43, Folder I.613)
  - Milan Knžk, 1965, undated; 18 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "2nd manifestation of Aktual Art," text in English and photographs. Inventory #s:[01948.1-76] (Box 43, Folder I.614)
  - Milan Knžk, 1964-1965, undated; 19 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Why Just So," text in English and photographs. Inventory #s:[01949.1-28] (Box 43, Folder I.615)
  - Milan Knžk, 1965, undated; 20 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "With some friends we folded a great many paper gliders...," text in English. (Box 43, Folder I.616)
  - Milan Knžk, 1965, undated; 21 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Game of War," text in Czech and English and photographs. Inventory #s:[01950.1-49] (Box 43, Folder I.617)
  - Milan Knžk, 1965, undated; 22 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "How my actions could be carried by others elsewhere," text in English. (Box 43, Folder I.618)
  - Milan Knžk, 1965, undated; 23 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Make a big paper glider," text in English and photographs. Inventory #s:[01951.1-33] (Box 43, Folder I.619)
  - Milan Knžk, 1965, undated; 24 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Games," text in English. (Box 43, Folder I.620)
  - Milan Knžk, 1965, undated; 25 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Walk through Prague," text in English. (Box 43, Folder I.621)
  - Milan Knžk, 1965, undated; 26 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Kalendř"/"A calendar," text in Czech and English. (Box 43, Folder I.622)
  - Milan Knžk, 1965-1966, undated; 27 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Inhabitants of a house selected at random were sent many packages with random things in them," texts in Czech and English. (Box 43, Folder I.623)
  - Milan Knžk, 1966, undated; 28 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Ausflug"/"Outing," text in Czech and English. (Box 43, Folder I.624)
  - Milan Knžk, 1966, undated; 29 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "A week," text in English. (Box 43, Folder I.625)
  - Milan Knžk, 1966, undated; 30 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "aktuln pozdrav"/"AKTUAL greeting," text in Czech and English. (Box 43, Folder I.626)
  - Milan Knžk, 1966, undated; 31 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Všichni ti, kteř c t...," text in Czech. (Box 43, Folder I.627)
  - Milan Knžk, 1967, undated; 32 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Keeping together manifestation," texts in Czech and English. (Box 43, Folder I.628)
  - Milan Knžk, 1967, undated; 33 of 101 performance/event files (photocopies) acquired from Milan Knžk: "Aktual - Live Otherwise," text in English and photographs. Inventory #s:[01952.1-13] (Box 43, Folder I.629)